Hello friends, welcome to Creative
Bank. So today we will talk about the PSU sector
stock and
see if this stock can perform in this way in the
future and what is the scope for it to move
forward in which country. So
let's start. So
this topic is Bank of Baroda.
If we talk about Bank of Baroda, if we
look at the business of the company, then it has built a good business
in it and if we
go somewhere, then to some extent it is a
bank which is somewhat related to
private banks in
providing services. If we talk about it, it
is a good bank, its service is also good, it provides
excellent service both online and offline.
If we talk about it here, then you will see that the
company is
opening accounts of all types including vitamin deposits. Along with this, if
you come to the launch, then the company is also providing home loans, call personal
printed gold and educational loans of all
types. Most probably, the company is
also providing loans.  And
you can also apply for home loan digitally.
If we talk about investment, then the company
is there in government deposit schemes, bones,
you can see it online too.
You can also open an account for these trading accounts.
In the insurance sector too, the
company has services which include life
insurance, general insurance, health
insurance, you can apply for that too
online.
If we talk about digital products, then the company is providing instant banking,
merchant payment solution
online.
And if we come to business, then
if you look at the business sector,
you can see the company in MS Word corporate. In
corporates, in
agriculture sector, international
banking, so everywhere startup banking,
pimples and accent remittance, the company
's business is spread and in every
segment, if we talk about it, then the
company has a good business
model and gradually by doing this and expanding it a
little bit digitally, more and
more of its business is done.  The
company is gradually trying to make it a service provider
and its performance is such that
if seen from the perspective, it
seems to be improving gradually
and if we talk about its age rates,
they are also reasonable rates and the company
also launches many types of offers. So
if we talk about Bank of Baroda,
its model is a good business
model and the
way its performance is
gradually, its performance
seems to be improving now, a life is
seen coming in it now and if we
look at it here, the way the company is providing services
through the app, if you look at it, there are
225 plus
services which it is providing through its mobile app
and 95% retail
banking service coverage is complete,
you can check it, you can do that, you can
chop it,
every type of service is available there, there is
also digital account opening and
experience.  You can see the design principles of PIMS
here, so that this Invest
Boro Shop can be of every kind.
Here, the design of this has been given, taps have been given so that
you can do your work
properly. If we talk about BOB World State, then
this PIN
date has been downloaded a lot.
If we talk about Invest Activate War, then it is around 9 million, so if
you see a good graph, then brother, their performance is definitely
showing these.
Along with this, if we talk about their subsidiaries, then
India
First Life Insurance, BOB
Financials, Baroda Mutual Fund, then this is
also intraday, Global Baroda Global Share
Service of BOB. And if we
talk about outside, if you look at the subsidy scheme of the year, then
in the state, there is their Bank
of Baroda in Uganda, in the world,
inside Andrew, then the company is
showing a very good performance.
If you come to the balance sheet, then if we
talk about net interest income, then you will
see here  You will see the total income in this,
but instead of total income in this,
it is seen increasing, operating profit is
also seen increasing, profit after
tax is also big, profit after
tax is also seen increasing,
write GPS Vijay Bharti, so in every way the
company is seen improving
itself and
gradually, gradually, the
profit is seen to be seen, if we look at
all these things, and the
second thing is that if you look at the market cap, then this
bank comes at number two after SBI in the Achieve sector, and
if we talk about small PSU banks, then there are very
few such banks which are
showing good performance, in this topic, this company has
seen a lot of performance in between,
but gradually, it is seen increasing,
along with Bank of Baroda, this is the
mixture and if we talk about here, but
gradually, it can be seen increasing, it can be
seen that the entire RBI and the government's efforts are becoming disgusting.  There
is support for gradually bringing in a bad bank as
well, work is going on ahead, keeping that in
mind, if we
talk about Bank of Baroda, it can
show a good performance from here if
you think about it in the long run, then according to that, if
you are thinking accordingly, then whatever
schemes of the government come,
these companies are
provided to these banks, the customer problems reach through these banks, so they
also get the benefit of those things, the
number of customers are
seen filling up, so there are many things from which they get
benefit, if we talk about that then
keep their patience in front of you, then the
GPS is around the stomach and if you
look here, then their market cap
is the market cap and if we talk here, then we will
see the face value, then let us
see once what their track record is
in terms of dividend,
if we look at the dividend then  The accounts are
completely backward. If we talk about bonuses, it has never been
said in it.
If we look at it from the revenue point of view, then
leaving aside 2017-18-19, then basic, a little bit of a
conch has definitely been seen in it, a
good increase has been seen in terms of
revenue. If we
look at the profitability of the company, then when this brinjal was
launched in 2018 and after that,
but if you look at the way it has
handled itself, if you look at it in 2019, then there is profit.
In between, the profit has decreased a little as
compared to 2019, but
whatever is there in it, it has compensated for it. There is a
good profit seen in 2021.
And here, if I talk about partner
partner performance, then if we look at it, then
they are seeing a mixed
performance. If we
look at 2020, then this near water portal has
seen good performance, provided if
such problems are seen coming in the future, then it is
better. The market is moving with the thought that
whatever they have  These banks should be changed on some days.
Now it remains to be seen
how many days they will change and
how much they can perform well.
If we talk about this, then if we
look at the share holding pattern here, it is a good
share holding pattern. However, if we
look at it, then the companies have removed their holding. If we look
here, then the
government has approximately 65
% ​​holding left. If we
look at FIR, then
BNP Paribas has a holding of
around 2%. LIC has also been
declared in this, HDFC, ICICI, Nippon
Life. So here and with Mutual Fund,
a good thing is that the holding
is present in it because they rely more on banks. If we talk about
Mirchi and Khand, which are a
type of debt funds, then if we talk about
pension funds,
they are a little more, so those who
want to buy stocks like that method.
Friends, if you liked this
video then definitely like it and
if you have not subscribed to my channel yet then
definitely subscribe to our channel.  And if you want to connect with
us through our membership program, then
you can search our channel
on your health related channel by the name of Betting Premium,
our membership program,
and you
can connect with us. So here, if we talk about the
chart pattern of Stop, Virgo is mainly
fine, it is gradually
improving its performance. Now if you look
at the chart here also, its
performance related to the bottom is seen improving,
but even here, if you look, the
stock still could
not take support above the resistance of 38.2%, it
is below it. In this range, even
if this chart has made a place from here, then also
it has not yet risen so much that
if seen, its trend will change.
Where will the trend change be?
Friends, it will come out above the paper of about one hundred and fifty rupees, one hundred and sixty-one.
Then, if seen here,
it still
needs about sixty-seventy rupees to come out. Now it remains to be seen whether it will
actually be seen
showing a performance from here or
not.  If we leave this area then we
should buy above 160 if seen in that way and
here as much as you can see this red line, the
red candle which is visible, there are
more candles than the green candidate, the red one is
this topic if seen but it is going on
slowly the performance is improving, the
performance of possibilities is emerging
now I will take you to the short way,
if you see from the long side
then there is absolutely no need to buy this stock, as it is
seen,
below the resistance of 30.2 percent, anyway there is
no desire to give, but
if we take this area
home a little here, then from here we take the area of ​​1st January and
2nd January 2021, so
if we look at this support zone, then
here if you will see that the stock is
in its police trend, that is, it is present above ₹90 as long as the
misfortune is in its bad
stand, this green candle is being formed, there is a
possibility that now this green
candle will move ahead  It should be seen taking a jump
and a buildup should be seen below. A
small stop loss should be placed on it. If
you are buying any bank, then
if we talk about Baroda Bank, this stock looks a little good
and its chart pattern is also good. It should
run a little further from here. The stop loss should be 15 rupees,
around the resistance of 50% below ₹10
and it can be sustained.
You will have to use a little more time frame
because in this way,
you can get a backlash at this red candle place
because these people may be trapped here, so
due to this, you can
definitely see a backlash. It can happen,
but
if you give it a little time, there is a possibility that these
stones may be seen moving upwards after some time
and for setting at an expense,
you must keep a stop loss of
315 rupees in it. It can be done gradually as per
their schemes and services.  The improvement in them is
visible and
the way the government's support is moving forward, the
work of bringing in the banks is going on,
it can come out of that, if we
see a change in fortunes, then it can be
taken from that perspective and
also a little from the perspective of the market and the way it is
coming out, we can get caught according to that, the
time frame will have to be kept a little more, a
time frame of one to one and a half years, why should we
take it and from here, if the way
this well is complete, the way it is going,
if its
performance improves a little and
in the coming time, within six months, nine months,
you will see that this
area is wide, this area of ​​consolidation
here is around 150-160, it can reach,
but you will have to give it a
good time frame, whatever the benefit is, otherwise
you can see here, the way a
decline is deep, the way there
is consolidation, the way there are plate candles, you
can see, but if
you look at this area, then the rate
You will see green candles more related to the candidate, that is why
you can see it from here,
it relieves stress, he can see it, do
your LIC once,
after that fold the stock taken from brother
and if there is any other career related to torque, then
you can ask us by commenting,
thank you to